List<Map<String, dynamic>> queAns = [
  {
    'question': "What is the capital of france?",
    'options': ['Berlin', 'Paris', 'Rome'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Paris'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which planet is known as red planet?",
    'options': ['Mars', 'Jupiter', 'Venus'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Mars'
  },
  {
    'question': " What Italian city is famous for its system of canals?",
    'options': ['Rome', 'Naples', 'Venice'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Venice'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which flies a green, white, and orange (in that order) tricolor flag?",
    'options': ['Ireland', 'Ivory Coast', 'Italy'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Ireland'
  },
  {
    'question': "What company makes the Xperia model of smartphone?",
    'options': ['Samsung', 'Sony', 'Nokia'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Sony'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which of the following is NOT a fruit?",
    'options': ['Rhubarb', 'Tomatoes', 'Avocados'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Rhubarb'
  },
  {
    'question': "Where was the first example of paper money used?",
    'options': ['China', 'Turkey', 'Greece'],
    'correctAnswer': 'China'
  },
  {
    'question': "What number was the Apollo mission that successfully put a man on the moon for the first time in human history?",
    'options': ['Apollo 11', 'Apollo 12', 'Apollo 13'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Apollo 11'
  },
  {
    'question': " Which of the following languages has the longest alphabet?",
    'options': ['Greek', 'Russian', 'Arabic'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Russian'
  },
  {
    'question': "The fear of insects is known as what?",
    'options': ['Entomophobia', 'Arachnophobia', 'Ailurophobia'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Entomophobia'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the largest US state (by landmass)?",
    'options': ['Texas', 'Alaska', 'California'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Alaska'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which app has the most total users?",
    'options': ['TikTok', 'Snapchat', 'Instagram'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Instagram'
  },
  {
    'question': " What city hosted the 2002 Olympic Games?",
    'options': ['Tokyo', 'Beijing', 'Sydney'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Sydney'
  },
  {
    'question': "How long did dinosaurs live on the earth?",
    'options': ['100-150 million years', '150-200 million years', '200+ million years'],
    'correctAnswer': '150-200 million years'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the strongest muscle in the human body?",
    'options': ['Jaw', 'Heart', 'Glutes'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Jaw'
  },
];